You can't handle the tooth.
Tooth Fairy is a comedy, family, fantasy film directed by Michael Lembeck.
When minor-league hockey player Derek Thompson -- who has a penchant for knocking out his opponents' teeth every time he plays
-- disillusions a fan, he is sentenced to a stint for one week as a bona fide, tutu-clad, real-life tooth fairy.
Soon, Derek is inspired to rekindle his youthful dreams.
Derek Thompson / Tooth Fairy, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Tracy, played by Stephen Merchant.
Carly, played by Ashley Judd.
Lily, played by Julie Andrews.
Mick Donnelly, played by Ryan Sheckler.
Ziggy, played by Seth MacFarlane.
Tooth Fairy is a 2010 fantasy comedy family film directed by Michael
Lembeck and produced by Jason Blum, Mark Ciardi and Gordon Gray.
It was written by Lowell Ganz, Babaloo Mandel, Randi Mayem Singer, Joshua
Sternin and Jennifer Ventimilia with music by George S.
Clinton, and stars Dwayne Johnson in the title
role, Ashley Judd, and Julie Andrews.
Filmed in Vancouver, British Columbia, it was co-produced by Walden Media and
distributed and theatrically released by 20th Century Fox on January 22, 2010.
The film was given a negative reception from critics.
It was commercially successful, grossing $112.5 million on a $48 million budget.
A direct-to-video sequel, Tooth Fairy 2, starred Larry the Cable Guy as
the title character and was released on March 6, 2012.
The film explores themes of fairy, ice hockey, tooth
fairy, tooth, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted.